Tristan Thorburn

(647) 382-9573 · tristanthorburn@gmail.com · LinkedIn · GitHub · Toronto, Canada

WEB DEVELOPER PROFILE

I am a front end developer who enjoys the challenge of translating the ideas and design of a project to a working and accessible site. I studied with Juno College in order to make the industry change from hospitality. My next goal is to further develop my knowledge in front and back end development with on the job experience, and look forward to hearing from your company.

TECH SKILLS / SUMMARY OF SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS3 / SASS / SCSS | JavaScript
React JS

RESTful APIs, Firebase

Git | GitHub
Web Accessibility | Responsive Design
Paired programming & team-based development
Project scope management

Conflict Resolution
Time Management

Leadership Self-sufficiency Communication Multi-tasking

Teamwork

RECENT PROJECTS

Under the Sea [Functionality](Skills: Javascript) - GitHub - Live Link

• This project provided experience using Javascript to manipulate the DOM in order to create a functioning hamburger menu and image carousel on mobile screens.

Under the Sea (Skills: HTML, CSS, SCSS, Responsive Design) - GitHub - Live Link

• Creating a multi-page website from a design with implementation of media queries for functionality on multiple screen sizes. During this project I used a mobile first design strategy, and manual drawing as no mobile design was provided.

One Magazine (Skills: HTML, CSS, SCSS) - GitHub - Live Link

• The purpose of this project was to practice the conversion of a design to a functional website, using mark-up planning techniques to strategize formatting the website through HTML and CSS.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Juno College, Toronto, Canada	2022
Web Development Bootcamp	
Juno College, Toronto, Canada	2022
Intro to Web Development Course	

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Well Hamilton Inc, Toronto & Hamilton, Canada

2021 – 2022

Assistant General Manager

- Structured Berg and Squirrel point of sale systems functionality for ease of use for staff.
- Updated company cash out and inventory excel sheets.
- Created and upheld restaurant policies for categories including general house, harassment, guest interaction, emergency, fire, medical and covid-19.

817 Sports Bar & Grill, Toronto, Canada

2018 - 2021

Assistant General Manager

- Interviewed, onboarded and trained all Front of House staff.
- Learned to operate, multitask and create solutions to problems arising from the operation of a brand-new venue.
- Lead the execution of 200 guest(s) venture events in tandem with the Chef.

817 Remington's Night Club, Toronto, Canada

2015 - 2018

Bartender

- Responsible for opening and closing duties, cash reconciliation, covering management duties and keys to venue
- Promoted by ownership to Assistant General Manager opening their new venue 817 Sports.